Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found.
We look through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious point's our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there, no regrets.
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
Almost there.
I can't wait to see the
look on all their faces
when they find out I
discovered the gold first.
Look at those ruins!
What's up with this place?
The ground's all crooked.
Guess I'll go this way.
Gold! Gold!
No, Holy!
Stay!
I said stay!
What was I thinking?
I'm too little to do this all by myself!
I should have gone back!
Interesting.
You're the third one to
make it this far today.
Who are you?
Can't believe that spider-headed
fool was so careless you
killed Geratsu didn't you I guess
he means that guy from earlier
I suppose it's for the best the world is
better off with one less
imbecile when you agree
Tripped over.
Calm yourself.
There's no need to be so afraid of Holy.
He's merely a pet.
He won't bite you.
What about this guy?
It looks like he's been
chewed up and spit out.
I assure you, Holy is a
very well-trained dog.
He would never bite anyone.
It was I who attacked that man.
Are you crazy? Who are you?
Why would you do something like that?
I am Skybreeder Ohm.
Now would you please be quiet?
This is a mistake.
This is too scary.
Do you think I'm not saddened
by what's taking place here?
Huh?
I don't understand.
Why do men choose to fight when they
must know how fragile their lives are?
I'm not really sure.
Man was put here to find happiness.
Yet time after time they
throw themselves into battle.
Only to lose their
lives along with the joy
they struggled so hard to
find what a strange and
tragic thing is man's
nature there is only one
way to be redeemed and
that is for all men to die.
Oh please sir you don't
really mean that do
you this is bad what
have you come here for?
Oh i was just trying to find the city
of gold greed only leads to ruin.
You must be rescued.
You want to rescue me?
Only losing your life will save
you from all your earthly desires.
He doesn't want to rescue me at all!
Kamakiri! Kamakiri!
Go.
Get out of here, Lock.
Why? Tell me.
Wiper.
He's headed for God's Shrine.
But Eneru isn't there.
There's still time, Lucky.
Stop, Wiper.
Alright, I understand.
Now quiet.
Save your strength.
Nobody can beat Eneru.
I am living lightning!
Lock, hear me.
He comes as lightning, an element that
man has feared from the beginning.
And rightly so.
He can't be conquered.
Don't worry, I'll stop Wiper.
You just wait here and save your energy.
I'm going to leave Isis' bag with you.
Nobody can beat Enoru.
He can't be conquered.
Kamakiri is so strong, yet
his will has been broken.
If what he said is true, then Enoru's
eaten a Logia-type Devil Fruit.
The most powerful kind of all.
I've got to stop Wiper
before it's too late.
Hmm.
I've been here.
It looks familiar.
Or have I?
Maybe.
Oh, maybe not.
I'm not sure.
Are you laughing at me? Huh?
What are you so worked up for anyway?
The only reason you came along in
the first place is to get some food.
My bad sense of direction
shouldn't matter.
You dummy.
No, no, no.
Hey, let go of that,
you better break, jerk.
There's no more food in there.
Hey, where are you taking us?
Of all the weird places to end up, huh?
It's a dead end!
You can't be serious.
I walked all this way.
Maybe, maybe it's a trick door.
Let's find out.
I can always try busting
through this stupid thing.
Come, come, bazooka!
But it, it didn't even butch.
Not again!
He didn't follow me. I'm okay.
I bet he's a priest, too.
But it looks like there's a lot
of places to hide around here.
If I can just stay hidden
long enough to escape,
I can try and meet up with the others.
I have to make sure he doesn't see me.
He looked like a swordsman, so if I
keep my distance, I should be okay.
Huh.
He's run quite a long way.
But running from salvation is futile.
Attachment to this life is
a result of evil desires.
Therefore...
The path to peace leads to but one place.
This is the ordeal of iron.
The survival rate is zero.
Isa?
I can't just sit here.
I've got to go find Lock.
Oh, no, you don't.
Wait, Isa!
Isa!
Get back here!
Leave me alone!
I've got to save Lock!
Let go!
I've got to get out of here right now!
This isn't any of your business!
Maybe it's not any of my business?
But there's no way I'm going to sit back!
and let a little kid get herself killed!
I'm a warrior!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Kid warrior.
Hey, those dirty looks don't
scare me, so knock it off!
Nami, is everything okay?
We're fine.
All right, stop messing
around and get the waver.
You don't understand.
You have to let me go so
I can save my friends.
I have to help them.
You better knock it off right
now or I'm going to slug you.
And no crying.
Look, you don't want to end up
like Sanji and Usopp, do you?
Well, do you?
Come on, I'll help you in the boat.
WAAA!
Huh?
Oh no.
Okay.
That was scary.
What's with this lame cave, anyhow?
First, there was an earthquake.
And a flood of ocean clouds.
I could have drowned.
You hear me?
Open up!
Why is it going crazy?
Let me out of here!
I've gone!
Deathling!
Nami, no! Whoa!
That way leads to the forest!
Mommy!
What do we do?
It's gone into the forest!
Missed! Ha!
You're lucky!
Huh?
What's that?
Who's that? I don't know!
Something's coming!
Go that way! That way!
Lord of the sky!
No way! Aissa!
We're inside the forest.
Um, hey, what's the idea?
Are you even listening to me?
I'm going to pluck you
and cook you up in a stew!
Hey, come on! Fly higher!
I don't want to be giant snake food!
Can't you fly any faster, you dumb bird!
It's still coming after us.
Something must have really pissed it off.
Why you!
To make it to God's Shrine, I have
to climb to the top of Giant Jack.
And if Eneru is there, it's time I
brought an end to our terrible history.
Once and for all.
Now.
Wiper, if you climb that vine any
farther, you'll reach God's shrine.
What makes you think you
have permission to pass?
Damn you.
It doesn't matter.
Adding for that shrine
is no longer useful.
Kon-Fo?
What business do you have here?
Still can't let go of your old position?
No, but I still have
responsibilities I've yet to fulfill.
I thought you might be interested in knowing
I've recently come from God's shrine.
It's tragic.
The entire thing's been utterly destroyed.
Naturally, Aniru was nowhere to be found.
Perhaps it means he no
longer has any need for it.
It appears that their years
of hard labor are over.
You see, this island is
no longer useful to me.
I've simply come to bid you farewell.
I demand to know ohm what is it
you and your master seek to do?
hold on you saying energy's not up there!
one of Straw Hats friends
That bird's going to pay.
It's you.
Where am I?
More ruins.
These guys all look pretty tough.
Oh, well.
Hey, hand over the gold.
Look what we have here.
If it isn't another greedy infidel
seeking his salvation, Enough!
Get out of my way or I'll
destroy every one of you!
The time has come, Om.
Tell me where Eneru and
the Divine Squad are.
You stupid cave!
Just let me out!
I'm sure you each feel what
you have to say is important.
But there's only one way for your voice to
be heard you must survive
or find salvation.
Let's go holy be as ferocious
as you want boy that one
is our target pierre since
he is the The most powerful,
we must neutralize Eneru's priest first!
I'm really getting sick of you, Snake.
I mean, how the hell'd you
get way up here anyway?
Oh, damn it!
One minute this place is
up, the other it's down.
This is one messed up cave.
Well, I guess the three of you...
will just have to die together!
You need to work on your aim there, pal.
Insolent blue sea dweller.
You think you can just come to this
land and take what's rightfully ours?
You have no idea how long
and hard we've struggled
if you sky people want to
blow each other to pieces.
That's your business
It's like I told that
priest I couldn't care less.
That figures I!
Should have finished you from the start.
Damn.
This guy's actually
tougher than I thought.
Now die!
All right, note to self.
Gotta watch out for those poisonous fangs.
Speaking of fangs.
Whoa.
Oh, I've never seen a dog move like that.
Not many people have, friend.
You'll find that Holy knows a great number
of commands beyond just sit and stay.
I'm a sky breeder, renowned
for my special animal training.
I've trained him how to
walk upright on two legs
and to box just like a
champion prize fighter.
Show him, Holy.
Nice doggie.
Godfar, you were already beaten by Shit.
Don't you know when to quit?
What do you really hope to do?
I doubt you even have enough
strength left to wield that spear.
I don't know what Eneru is plotting,
but I will stop him with
my dying breath if need be.
There's no way a washed-up god like you
could ever understand
Eneru's noble thoughts.
Godfile, you're a foolish old man, a
man that doesn't have long to live.
After them!
Don't let the Shendorians escape!
What the?
Hey, you hear that?
It sounded like... goats!
The Divine Squad!
If they catch us, they'll kill us!
The Divine Squad? Who are they?
They're Aniru's soldiers!
Get us out of here now!
I'd love to, but in case you haven't
noticed, I have no idea where we're going!
That stupid snake keeps getting in my way!
Chopper! No!
I'm coming! Hang on!
I see.
He was part of your Blue Sea crew.
Hey, watch his step over there.
What the...
Barbed wire?
So that's his ordeal.
Chopper, talk to me!
Say something! Why?
Why did you try and take this guy on?
Come on!
A shame, isn't it?
Those barbs, Iron Cloud.
Their light is a cloud, but hard as iron.
blown into shape by a milky dial.
I've rigged several of
them with hidden triggers.
You and your little friend found out the
hard way what happens when you step on one.
This field is a weapon.
I don't have to attack you.
I can sit back and watch your
own blundering do you in.
I'm partially responsible for that
animal's defeat, but he's also to blame.
He stumbled into my ordeal all by himself.
I guess you'll want to
get revenge now, huh? No.
Believe it or not, I normally don't
like fighting for that reason at all.
Oh.
I'm actually impressed. Normally.
But you've changed my mind.
Well, Conis, I think we've arrived.
This is the seashore where our Blue Sea
friends are planning to meet, right?
Yes, Father.
This is where Nami told me
they'd be dropping anchor.
Well, then what should we do now?
I really wasn't expecting
to look after their ship.
Nonetheless, we must protect it
at all costs until they return.
I'll sound the horn to scare
off any threats. Right.
Good idea, Father.
Let them hear our resolve.
Ah, perfect.
Keep your eyes open, Sue.
I'm counting on you to keep watch.
Hang on.
I'll nurse both of you back to health.
You'll be better in no time.
Please, everyone, be safe.
I'm sorry the Sky Island is like this.
Don't stop until we've taken Edaru's head!
The only heads that are
all are yours, Shandora!
Climb up to your church!
Don't let them get to God's shrine! No!
Wiper, please don't
use the reject anymore!
Now, Divine Squad!
Let's kill them all!
Don't challenge Eneru, Wiper!
He can't be defeated,
no matter what we do!
That's right,
those of you still in the game,
climb your way to the upper
ruins and destroy each other.
There will only be five survivors.
My words and prophecies are absolute!
Stop this insanity now, Wiper!
I'm not here to...
You're not what, old man?
You believe that you're not my enemy?
To the Shandians, there's no
difference between you and Eneru!
Both of you must go!
Quit being stubborn!
Listen to reason!
Damn you!
My burn bazooka didn't
even faze that thing.
What are those scales made of?
No!
No more!
I'm sick of this!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
What... was that?
Hm.
Typical Blue Sea Dweller,
you didn't expect it.
You see, this sword of mine
is also made of Iron Cloud.
In other words,
the blade itself is actually
Iron Cloud expelled from
a dial that's conveniently
embedded in the sword's hilt.
And it will hunt its prey
to the ends of the earth!
Well, do you understand it better
now, swordsman from the Blue Sea?
Yeah, it's just like a whip.
I get it.
You white, white sea people are more
circus performers than warriors.
Holy, we're going to
have to fight separately.
From the sound of things, the Upper
Ruins are about to get very busy.
The Sky Knight.
I didn't expect him to be here.
We're here to assist you, oh mighty Ohm.
Look who's here.
Well, you know what this means.
Yeah, it means we're the only ones left.
Don't worry, Wiper.
We'll help you get to Eneru
and take his head off.
Hey, wait.
That should work.
I'll just dig my way out.
That giant snake!
It's laughing?
Hold it!
Would you ghosts just leave us alone?
Nami, Aissa, noob!
Kill them both!
Aisa, what are you doing here? What the?
Nami, what are you doing here?
Hey, Throw, what's happening? Wiper!
What is it you're plotting
here, Blue Sea Dweller?
Aisa, get away from that woman!
Huh?
That was close. Wiper!
You're a monster!
Why did you two come to
such a perilous place?
We didn't mean to.
We were chased by this giant snake.
Ah!
You idiot! Oh shit!
Issie...
WIPER!
You were so distracted that you
neglected to protect yourselves.
Quit worrying about other people!
Accept it.
There's nothing you can do to save them.